<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="101">
    <author>Ozz</author>
    <version>1.2.0.1</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_taskList.dds</iconFilename>
    <title>
        <en>Task List</en>
        <de>Aufgabenliste</de>
        <fr>Liste Des Tâches</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
            <en><![CDATA[Task List

If you find yourself taking notes of what tasks you need to do, or even using external software, then Task List is here to help.

On the main menu, just above Settings, you will find a new menu with a clipboard icon. Use this menu to get started with the following features:

- Create groups to contain related tasks, such as Field 10 or General Farm Tasks.
- Create one-off tasks or tasks that recur daily, monthly, every N months, or every N days.
- Give tasks a priority so you know what to do first.
- Buy a new field and want to copy tasks from an existing field? No problem, you can do this in seconds.
- Got lots of fields and want to manage them as one? Create a template and use that repeatedly.
- View currently due tasks in the menu and mark them complete when you've done them.
- Plan ahead by looking at cumulative effort throughout the year. Also look ahead at the coming 12 months to see what tasks are coming up.
- View currently due tasks without checking the menu by pressing Shift + T
- Automatically track levels for animal food, conditions and production levels.

- Github:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_TaskList

Changelog:

1.2.0.1:
- Updated 'Every N month tasks to support 24 and 36 month recurrence. You can also set the start month. This is to better support setting up crop rotation schedules for groups or templates.
- Fixed a display bug where some tasks would incorrectly show as overdue.

1.2.0.0:
- Fix issue where tasks could not be saved if they had become invalid (e.g. due to missing fill types)

1.1.0.12:
- Improve handling of missing fill types in tasks, to avoid losing tasks when mods or updates change fill type ids.

1.1.0.11:
- Move to store fill types by name instead of id, to avoid issues when mods or updates change fill type ids.
- Some fill type related tasks may need to be re-added after this update

1.1.0.10:
- Disable the filter for text inputs, which caused words like Grass to be censored.
- Add Italian translation, thanks to FirenzeIT

1.1.0.9:
- Change evaluation to account for empty production/husbandry levels triggering a task
- Increase number priority and repetition options

1.1.0.8:
- Fix showing tasks for all farms in the workload view in multiplayer games
- Attempt to fix an issue where 'auto' tasks vanish in multiplayer games
- Add Turkish translation, with credit to Cyber-Syntax

1.1.0.7:
- Fix a bug when deleting a template instance
- Sort groups in the Manage Groups dialog by name

1.1.0.6:
- Limit active tasks shown with Shift + T to only those for the current farm
- Add Dutch translation, with credit to Nozem1982
- Add Russian translation, with credit to nik-conder

1.1.0.5:
- Multiplayer fix where auto tasks from previous version would prevent tasks being sent to the client
- Note: Some auto tasks (food, straw etc) may need to be re-added with this update

1.1.0.4:
- Fixed multiplayer issue where tasks would lose connection to the associated placeable between sessions
- Ensure auto tasks show as due when joining a multiplayer game

1.1.0.3:
- Updated dialog layouts to improve readability for lower resolutions.
- Improved German translations, with credit to MeRida2104.
- Fixed a multiplayer bug when changing farms
- Fixed a multiplayer bug where active tasks were not being shown

1.1.0.0:
- Added tracking tasks for animal conditions e.g slurry, straw etc
- You can now track the total food level for a husbandry
- You can now track inputs and outputs for productions
- Fixed a non-damaging error when saving
- Fixed bug with sending client state in multiplayer

]]></en>		
    <de><![CDATA[Aufgabenliste

Wenn Sie Notizen über die Aufgaben machen, die Sie erledigen müssen, oder sogar externe Software verwenden, dann ist Task List hier, um Ihnen zu helfen.

Auf dem Hauptmenü, direkt oberhalb von Einstellungen, finden Sie ein neues Menü mit einem Klarstreifen-Symbol. Verwenden Sie dieses Menü, um mit den folgenden Funktionen zu beginnen:

- Erstellen Sie Gruppen, um verwandte Aufgaben zu speichern, wie zum Beispiel Feld 10 oder allgemeine Bauarbeiten.
- Erstellen Sie eine einmalige Aufgabe oder eine Aufgabe, die täglich, monatlich, jeden N Monaten oder jeden N Tage wiederholt wird.
- Geben Sie Aufgaben eine Priorität, damit Sie wissen, was Sie zuerst tun sollen.
- Kaufen Sie ein neues Feld und möchten Sie Aufgaben von einem bestehenden Feld kopieren? Kein Problem, Sie können dies in Sekunden tun.
- Haben Sie viele Felder und möchten Sie sie als einen verwalten? Erstellen Sie ein Modell und verwenden Sie es wiederholt.
- Siehen Sie die aktuell fälligen Aufgaben im Menü an und markieren Sie sie als abgeschlossen, wenn Sie sie abgeschlossen haben.
- Planen Sie im Voraus, indem Sie den kumulativen Effort über das ganze Jahr betrachten. Siehen Sie auch im Voraus die nächsten 12 Monate an, um zu sehen, welche Aufgaben sich ankommen.
- Siehen Sie die aktuell fälligen Aufgaben ohne, dass Sie das Menü überprüfen, indem Sie Shift + T drücken.
- Automatisch die Nährstoffe und die Umweltbedingungen für Tiere verfolgen, sowie die Produktionsniveaus.

- Github:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_TaskList

Änderungsliste:

1.2.0.0:
- Beheben Sie ein Problem, bei dem Aufgaben nicht gespeichert werden konnten, wenn sie ungültig geworden waren (z. B. aufgrund fehlender Fülltypen)

1.1.0.12:
- Verbesserung der Handhabung fehlender Fülltypen in Aufgaben, um zu vermeiden, dass Aufgaben verloren gehen, wenn Mods oder Updates die Fülltyp-IDs ändern.

1.1.0.11:
- Fülltypen werden nun nach Namen statt nach ID gespeichert, um Probleme zu vermeiden, wenn Mods oder Updates die Fülltyp-IDs ändern.
- Einige Aufgaben im Zusammenhang mit Fülltypen müssen nach diesem Update möglicherweise erneut hinzugefügt werden.

1.1.0.10:
- Deaktivierung des Filters für Texteingaben, der zur Zensur von Wörtern wie „Gras“ führte.
- Italienische Übersetzung hinzugefügt, danke an FirenzeIT

1.1.0.9:
- Änderung der Auswertung, um leere Produktions-/Tierhaltungsebenen zu berücksichtigen, die eine Aufgabe auslösen.
- Erhöhung der Nummernpriorität und Wiederholungsoptionen

1.1.0.8:
- Beheben Sie das Anzeigen von Aufgaben für alle Bauern im Arbeitslastansicht in Mehrspielerspielen
- Versuchen Sie, ein Problem zu beheben, bei dem 'automatische' Aufgaben in Mehrspielerspielen verschwinden
- Turkische Übersetzung hinzufügen, mit Kredit an Cyber-Syntax

1.1.0.7:
- Beheben Sie einen Fehler beim Löschen einer Vorlageninstanz
- Sortieren Sie Gruppen im Dialogfeld „Gruppen verwalten“ nach Namen

1.1.0.6:
- Beschränken Sie die anzeigten aktiven Aufgaben mit Shift + T auf diejenigen des aktuellen Bauern
- Hinzufügen einer niederländischen Übersetzung, mit Kredit zu Nozem1982
- Hinzufügen einer russischen Übersetzung, mit Kredit zu nik-conder

1.1.0.5:
- Multiplayer-Fix, bei dem automatische Aufgaben aus der vorherigen Version das Senden von Aufgaben an den Client verhinderten
- Hinweis: Einige automatische Aufgaben (Lebensmittel, Stroh usw.) müssen mit diesem Update möglicherweise erneut hinzugefügt werden

1.1.0.4:
- Problem im Mehrspielermodus behoben, bei dem Aufgaben zwischen den Sitzungen die Verbindung zum zugehörigen platzierbaren Objekt verloren.
- Stellen Sie sicher, dass automatische Aufgaben beim Beitritt zu einem Multiplayer-Spiel als fällig angezeigt werden

1.1.0.3:
- Dialoglayouts wurden aktualisiert, um die Lesbarkeit bei niedrigeren Auflösungen zu verbessern.
- Verbesserte deutsche Übersetzungen, mit Dank an MeRida2104.
- Ein Multiplayer-Fehler beim Farmwechsel wurde behoben.
- Ein Multiplayer-Fehler wurde behoben, bei dem aktive Aufgaben nicht angezeigt wurden.

1.1.0.0:
- Hinzugefügt wurden Aufgaben zum Überwachen der Tierbedingungen, z.B. Dünger, Futter etc.
- Jetzt können Sie den gesamten Nährstoffwert für eine Tierhaltung verfolgen
- Jetzt können Sie die Eingänge und Ausgänge für die Produktion verfolgen
- Korrigiert wurde ein nicht schädlicher Fehler beim Speichern
- Korrigiert wurde der Bug mit dem Client-State in Multiplayer

]]></de>	
    <fr><![CDATA[Liste Des Tâches

Si vous vous retrouvez à prendre des notes des tâches que vous devez accomplir, ou même à utiliser un logiciel externe, alors Task List est là pour vous aider.

Sur le menu principal, juste au-dessus des Paramètres, vous trouverez un nouveau menu avec un icône de papier-collant. Utilisez ce menu pour commencer avec les fonctionnalités suivantes :

- Créez des groupes pour contenir des tâches liées, telles que le champ 10 ou les tâches agricoles générales.
- Créez des tâches uniques ou des tâches qui se répètent quotidiennement, mensuellement, chaque N mois ou chaque N jours.
- Donnez aux tâches une priorité pour savoir quoi faire en premier.
- Achetez un nouveau champ et voulez copier des tâches d'un champ existant ? Pas de problème, vous pouvez le faire en quelques secondes.
- Avez-vous beaucoup de champs et voulez les gérer comme un seul ? Créez un modèle et utilisez-le à plusieurs reprises.
- Affichez les tâches actuellement en retard dans le menu et marquez-les complétées lorsque vous les avez terminées.
- Plannez à l'avance en regardant l'effort cumulé tout au long de l'année. Regardez également à l'avance les 12 prochains mois pour voir ce qui se présente.
- Affichez les tâches actuellement en retard sans vérifier le menu en appuyant sur Shift + T.
- Suivre automatiquement les niveaux de nourriture et les conditions pour les animaux, ainsi que les niveaux de production.

- Github:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_TaskList

Journal des modifications:

1.2.0.0:
- Correction d'un problème où les tâches ne pouvaient pas être enregistrées si elles devenaient invalides (par exemple, en raison de types de remplissage manquants).

1.1.0.12:
- Amélioration de la gestion des types de remplissage manquants dans les tâches, afin d'éviter la perte de tâches lorsque des mods ou des mises à jour modifient les identifiants de types de remplissage.

1.1.0.11:
- Stockage des types de remplissage par nom plutôt que par identifiant, afin d'éviter les problèmes liés aux modifications des identifiants des types de remplissage par les mods ou les mises à jour.
- Certaines tâches liées aux types de remplissage devront peut-être être réajoutées après cette mise à jour.

1.1.0.10:
- Désactivation du filtre de saisie de texte, qui entraînait la censure de mots comme Grass.
- Ajout de la traduction italienne, grâce à FirenzeIT.

1.1.0.9:
- Modification de l'évaluation pour tenir compte des niveaux de production/élevage vides déclenchant une tâche
- Augmentation de la priorité numérique et des options de répétition

1.1.0.8:
- Correction de l'affichage des tâches pour tous les agriculteurs dans la vue de la charge de travail dans les jeux multijoueurs
- Essayez de résoudre un problème où les tâches automatiques disparaissent dans les jeux multijoueurs
- Ajouter une traduction turque, avec crédit à Cyber-Syntax

1.1.0.7:
- Correction d'un bug lors de la suppression d'une instance de modèle
- Trier les groupes dans la boîte de dialogue Gérer les groupes par nom

1.1.0.6:
- Limiter les tâches actives affichées avec Shift + T à celles du fermier actuel
- Ajouter une traduction néerlandaise, avec crédit à Nozem1982
- Ajouter une traduction russe, avec crédit à nik-conder

1.1.0.5:
- Correction multijoueur où les tâches automatiques de la version précédente empêchaient l'envoi des tâches au client
- Hinweis: Einige automatische Aufgaben (Lebensmittel, Stroh usw.) müssen mit diesem Update möglicherweise erneut hinzugefügt werden

1.1.0.4:
- Correction d'un problème multijoueur où les tâches perdaient la connexion au placement associé entre les sessions
- Assurez-vous que les tâches automatiques s'affichent comme dues lorsque vous rejoignez une partie multijoueur

1.1.0.3: 
- Mise à jour de la disposition des dialogues pour une meilleure lisibilité en basse résolution.
- Traductions allemandes améliorées, grâce à MeRida2104.
- Correction d'un bug multijoueur lors du changement de ferme.
- Correction d'un bug multijoueur empêchant l'affichage des tâches actives.

1.1.0.0 :
- Ajout de tâches de suivi pour les conditions d'animaux, par exemple la poudre, le foin, etc.
- Vous pouvez maintenant suivre le niveau total de nourriture pour une élevage
- Vous pouvez maintenant suivre les entrées et sorties pour les productions
- Corrigé une erreur non déstructive lors de la sauvegarde
- Corrigé le bug avec l'état client en multi-joueur

]]></fr>	
    </description>
	<extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="TL_SHOW_TASKS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_t" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="TL_SHOW_TASKS" />
    </actions>
</modDesc>